{
    "subject": "resource/John_Denver",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/Tina_Turner",
    "human_readable": "John Denver was associated with Tina Turner.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9460124969482422,
            "question": "What is known about the relationship between John Denver and Tina Turner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8763098120689392,
            "question": "Is there any evidence of a public connection between John Denver and Tina Turner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8695258498191833,
            "question": "Who was John Denver associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8428313732147217,
            "question": "Did John Denver and Tina Turner collaborate on music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8376774191856384,
            "question": "Why might someone be interested in the connection between John Denver and Tina Turner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8362910151481628,
            "question": "Were John Denver and Tina Turner part of the same musical genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8234535455703735,
            "question": "Did John Denver and Tina Turner ever perform together?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.766552209854126,
            "question": "How did John Denver's music compare to Tina Turner's?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.028051404282450676,
            "question": "What impact did their association have on either artist's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.019049732014536858,
            "question": "What events in their careers might have led to their association?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Denver was associated with Tina Turner.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7860_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did their association have on either artist's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7860_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did John Denver's music compare to Tina Turner's?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7860_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did John Denver and Tina Turner ever perform together?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7860_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7860_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7860_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7860_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7860_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7860_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7860_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7860_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7860_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7860_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7860_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that John Denver invited Tina Turner to perform on his TV special \"John Denver & The Ladies\" in 1979 and they performed a duet named \"Downhill Stuff\". This information supports the statement that John Denver was associated with Tina Turner."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "John Denver was associated with Tina Turner during a TV special performance, but they were not long-term musical partners or members of the same group.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There are multiple mentions of John Denver and Tina Turner performing together on a television special and recording a duet.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There are multiple sources confirming John Denver and Tina Turner performing a duet together during his TV special \"John Denver and the Ladies\" in 1979.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "John Denver and Tina Turner only performed a duet together during a TV special in 1979, and there is no information suggesting they had a longer association or were significantly connected beyond that single performance.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}